A hope!
Let's go.
995!
996!
997!
998!
999!
99!
And now for some magic boosting moguro leaf juice!
So gross!
Alright! Time for another round!
Still gross!
You want a swig birdie?
Or not.
Yeah, I got me a grimoire.
So what if I've got no magic?
I'm gonna kick butt anyway!
Okay!
Here we go!
Back to work!
1001!
I bet Yuno's doing some special training too!
He won't get the best of me!
YAAAH!
Determined to succeed despite his lack of magic, Asta was training hard for the Magic Knight's entrance exam, which would be held at the Clover Kingdom's capital in six months' time.
And indeed, so would Yuno.
That's enough for today.
Maybe a little more.
He'll be training too.
One thousand one!
Now break!
Both young men had their sights set on becoming the Wizard King.
One thousand five hundred and three!
Now, you know I can understand.
But encouraging Asta to take the exam, really? Are you certain?
Well, why not? Asta insists on taking it, so what else should I do?
We had some other promising youngsters.
It's impossible. There's just no way.
We'll never be Magic Knights.
That guy was insanely powerful, and they kicked him out of the ranks!
We just can't!
We're sorry, sir!
But unfortunately, it appears they've had a change of heart.
Okay, you know I understand, but does Asta really have a chance?
Well, he insists on taking it, so what else should I do?
You know I can understand, but I don't see the point in Asta going too.
Yes, well, he insists on taking it, so what else should I do?
Oh, I see the problem here.
You're going to be lonely when Asta leaves for the capital, aren't you?
That's so sweet, Father!
He's totally off the mark!
It's just if Asta's going to fail anyway, wouldn't it be better for him not to take it in the first place?
And the little ones!
They'll miss him terribly, I'm sure!
This isn't about me!
I'm just thinking of the children, that's all!
Don't give me that look!
That goes for you, too!
I know I'm going to miss Yuno and Asta when they leave for the city.
You're not alone.
Well, I've raised them since they were infants and spent all these years living alongside them.
It's only natural that I'd miss them a bit.
I understand.
We've always looked out for them and kept them safe.
But now, we must give them a chance to make their own way.
Yes, exactly.
Look at it like this.
Yuno may well succeed, but in all likelihood Asta will not, and he'll turn right around and come back.
Yes!
You're right!
He probably will!
Okay, then!
Yuno may be lost to us, but Asta sure to come back!
Now, about that book of Asta's.
Do you think it could truly be a grimoire?
It seems so unlikely.
Why would he get one if he can't use magic?
No clue.
However, that book...
Go on?
Nothing.
Well, what do you think?
My fairy own grimoire!
I don't know how it happened, but I got one!
The five leaf clover.
Who would have thought?
Training doesn't stop till I reach the church!
Coming through!
Made it!
Hey!
I'm back!
How's training?
Well, who got here first?
It's a close call, but Yuno was a tiny bit faster.
Seriously?
Were you really watching?
All right, then.
Let's see who's first into the church.
Looks like that would be it.
I didn't expect Yuno to be so childish.
You must have snapped with all the training we're doing.
It's getting pretty intense.
Though, we'll have Firewood for years.
I'm gonna be the Wizard King.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Nash. Is something up?
Nothing much. Just bored, that's all. Thought I'd spend some time making fun of a dumb dummy doing dumb stuff.
This isn't dumb, you punk!
Yeah, it really is. I mean, you can't even use magic, and you're taking the Magic Knights exam. There's no way you'll pass.
I wouldn't be too sure about that. Look. I've got a grimoire now and everything. I'll get into a Magic Knights squad. I know I will.
And then someday, I'll become the wizard-
No, you won't!
You're poor like the rest of us. An orphaned cast-off. Kids like us don't get to have dreams.
Hey, Nash.
No giving up, you hear me? We can dream as much as we want to!
No, you're wrong! We can't do anything!
We can! Look! I'm following my dreams!
Even if you're a poor orphan, you can become great just like anyone else. You can do anything you want, make your dreams come true, and make the people you care about happy!
That's exactly what I'm going to prove!
Come on.
I'll join the Magic Knights! And be the Wizard King!
Watch!
Wow!
So now, Asta and Yuno are heading to the Royal capital tomorrow, after all. I thought we'd send them off in style!
I thought we'd send them off in style.
It's quite a feast.
Father went to a bunch of villages.
He got all the paw potatoes he could.
No, Father!
Don't look at me like that!
It isn't just for you.
Honestly, I mainly did it for Yuno.
Father!
It's true.
Yuno just might make it into the Magic Knights.
But you...
Father!
Now listen.
It's a tough exam.
There's no shame in failing, Asta.
It's not like anybody expects you to pass.
I can't even tell if you're cheering me on or putting me down right now!
You'll always have a place here, alright?
No matter what, this is your home.
Even if it is a crumbling dump, it's still your home.
Yeah, and don't ever forget it.
We're gonna miss you so much while you're gone, Asta.
And Yuno too.
Yeah, cause we're family!
You're gonna say all that stuff to Yuno too, right?
About how he can always come back?
Yes, well, he'll be fine.
Hey now!
You may not think so, but I'll be fine too!
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
Then I'll come back for Sister Lily!
And when I do, I'll ask her to marry me!
Let's all eat now, shall we?
Boiled pot-potatoes, battered pot-potatoes, roasted pot-potatoes or fried, sautéed pot-potatoes and steamed too!
Boiled pot-potatoes a la hage, pot-potato juice, and extra special pot-potato flog.
Thank you!
It looks so yummy!
Ow!
It's only a little bit burnt, so good!
I got this on this one!
Don't hug it all for yourself, you big pig!
Delicious!
Take care, boys!
You know, you'll ride us, won't you?
Of course.
I hope you guys have fun!
But come back soon, okay?
Asta will be back soon enough, don't you worry.
Come on, Nash!
But listen, if by some chance, some very small one, you actually manage to join the Magic Knights...
Yeah, what?
Then I'll start believing dreams really can come true!
That I can be anything I want!
And maybe one day I'll become a Magic Knight too!
Or, you know, whatever.
I'll be waiting.
Sure.
Alright, Asta, let's get going.
Hey, hold up, Yuno!
Do you have to be such a jerk all the time, Lady Killer?
Sure, we're rivals.
That doesn't mean we can't be friends.
You know.
See you later!
Wish us luck, everybody!
Have a safe trip!
Good luck!
So long.
Yuno and Asta, so strange to watch them leave.
I can't believe how much they've grown.
Asta's always had that boundless energy from the day we met.
Everybody, I'd like you to meet our new arrival, Sister Lily.
Let's give her a warm welcome.
Sister Lily?
Yes?
Pretty please, will you marry me?
Ah!
Oh, I didn't mean to!
Sorry!
Just for Lily.
Oh boy, he's lost it now.
Yuno may not like to admit it, but Asta changed him.
Made him stronger, more determined.
Asta.
His injuries are very bad.
It's my fault he's hurt.
He was just trying to defend me.
From what?
Yuno, what happened?
Asta, stay with us!
Sister Lily, I'm here.
Will you marry me?
He'll be alright.
Good luck, boys.
We're proud of you.
Summer.
After months of training, Asta and Yuno have finally set out for the Royal Capital to take the Magic Knight's entrance exam.
The capital is a far distance from Hajj, and their journey will be a long one.
The capital, eh?
What do you think it's gonna be like?
Wonder if we'll meet the Wizard King?
First, we have to pass the Magic Knight's entrance exam.
And then, who knows?
Oh man, I can't wait!
You can't?
Aren't you nervous, though?
Huh?
About what?
How very Asta.
Let's get a move on, huh?
Got a long way to go!
Hey!
I gotta be the Wizard King like yesterday!
It doesn't matter when you get there.
It won't make you the Wizard King any sooner.
And once I am the Wizard King?
Asta, is that you?
How grand you've become!
Sister, I mean my darling Lily.
I've come for you just as I promised I would.
I am the Wizard King now.
Hop on, my dear.
Yes!
Hold on tight for the ride of your life.
It'll be great!
Can you even fly a broom?
Without any magic.
Yeah, sure, I'll make it work!
Will you now?
Totally!
I'm sure my trusty grimoire will help me.
As long as you don't give up, you can do anything!
Come on, let's move!
Do you want to get left behind?
We'll keep training till we reach the capital!
Sure we will.
Bet you can't catch me!
No, not done yet!
Stop this!
So much further to go.
Not yet!
Still going!
I wish everybody back home could get to try this too.
Yeah.
This way!
Actually, this way.
Hey, wait up!
Stay out of my way!
Calm down.
I was just helping you.
Well, I don't need your help.
Gotcha!
At first, I'll kill you.
Yeah!
Why'd you stop?
Oh, wow.
It's huge.
The capital, finally.
That's where the Wizard King is.
Here we go.
Time to do this thing.
Hope you're ready, because I'm coming.
I will be the Wizard King.
Yeah!
After a long journey,
Asta and Yuno have finally arrived
at the royal capital of the Clover Kingdom.
Awaiting them there
is the Magic Knight's entrance exam.
If they are to join a Magic Knight squad,
they must face off
against one mighty foe after another.
As it are a few days.
I feel right now.
can't be lost
closed the first幕 in a large room
I would also believe that it's a result
the story comes from good news
I've been thinking a lot, but I've been thinking a lot, but I want to laugh.
I want to be what I want to do, and I want to be what I want to do.
I can't say it is what I want to do.
The Mystery of the Grimoires
What happened?
I think... we've shrunk.
Anyway, like I was saying, my grimoire and yours are totally different.
Okay.
A grimoire's measurements, its size, thickness, etc., are determined by its owner's talent.
Alright then, let's compare grimoires. Come on, hand it over.
No way.
Why not? You're afraid you'll lose, aren't you?
Not a chance.
Hey! Don't get so cocky just because the girls kinda like you.
Let it go.
Come on, you know! We've always wanted to be Magic Knights.
This is the first step on the road to becoming the Wizard King.
Black Clover, page 4.
The Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
My magic is never giving up!